[
    {
        "question": "-25+5",
        "answer": -20
    },
    {
        "question": "100%10",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "100/100*10",
        "answer": 10.0
    },
    {
        "question": "3*5+8*6",
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "question": "3*5+8*6/2",
        "answer": 39.0
    },
    {
        "question": "3*5+8*6/2",
        "answer": 39.0
    },
    {
        "question": "3*5+8*6/2/3",
        "answer": 23.0
    },
    {
        "question": "3+4",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "4%2",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "4/100*2",
        "answer": 0.08
    },
    {
        "question": "2/100*4",
        "answer": 0.08
    },
    {
        "question": "2+6-7/5*6",
        "answer": -0.3999999999999986
    }
]